This guy's the new Emperor?
Hold up, he could just be a gofer.
G-Good. Come with me.
I'll take you to the Emperor.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
An apartment with a basement?
Pretty run-of-the-mill for the Emperor.
Whoa...
This way.
In here.
Way to show up, Mr. Unarmed and Butt Naked!
Is that...
Indeed, I am Emperor Rahazelt!
Now, regarding your actions yesterday...
I shall disregard it out of pure mercy!
Screw this kid!
Ah, you're younger than I expected!
As for myself, you'd be surprised to know
I'm actually 1,300,000 years old!
Is he trying to get a rise out of me?
For what, exactly?
God, he's annoying.
Not good, calm down.
This may be a strategy
to sniff out my identity...
D-Don't kid me like that, sir.
I'm pleased to meet you...
Second Emperor.
Hey, making up my age didn't work, for real.
Of course not.
These guys better be kidding...
I mean, they can't be serious.
They do think I'm some nutcase
that exposed himself, after all.
Who are you kidding with that insane number?
You think so, for real?
Explains why they're so relaxed.
I guess that makes things easier, though.
What's your name?
I'm Raion Ouno. Here's my ID.
So? What's your objective?
Proof of Identification
This identification proves that the individual
below is a student at the listed school.
Grade: 8th Grade, Class 3
Name: Raion Ouno
School Name: City of Suginami
Suginami West Fifth Middle School
I had a lot of questions to ask you, like...
How you killed with Tasuketsu, and stuff...
A multitude of methods. What else?
They don't seem suspicious based on
their answers and overall demeanor.
They may have been faking as the Emperor,
but the daily announcements
must have come from them.
Which would make my next move...
I share a lot of values with the Emperor,
so I came hoping to help in any way I can!
Let's find out... if you're
my enemy or my ally!
What values do you mean?
Values about Tasuketsu, of course!
People nowadays take life
so lightly. Good riddance!
Hey, kiddo. Is that really how you feel?
Huh?
Was that girl there a second ago?
I'm asking you a question.
Tell me the truth.
Are you serious? Why would
I be honest when I'm probing?
Go on. Did you mean what you just said?
Of course I didn't, you idiot!
If I was in front of the Emperor with
a weapon, I'd beat them 10,000 times!
So that's your truth.
Beating someone 10,000 times...
is pretty intense, for real.
Well, well. Now what?
W-What happened?! How?!
I didn't even mean to...
It was her!
For whatever reason, I couldn't
lie in response to her question!
What the hell's going on?
Who are these guys?!
Hey, take it easy. So you're against
the Emperor behind Tasuketsu, right?
Then we're probably
on the same side, for real!
All right, then...
Let's hear your full story, for real.
There's no use in lying,
as you've probably figured out.
I'm not sure I can trust them,
but I do know that they've definitely
got the upper hand here.
We'll get to the details later.
Just give us the gist of your situation.
I wanted to see the current Emperor.
One month ago, Tasuketsu suddenly began
at the hands of someone named the Emperor,
and it killed off most of humanity...
But out of nowhere came
an announcement that it had ended.
As of this moment,
Tasuketsu has concluded.
As of this moment, Tasuketsu has concluded.
I was lucky enough to survive, but I couldn't
make sense of anything that had happened.
I had a hunch that the current Emperor was
separate from the Emperor that held Tasuketsu.
That threw me for even more of a loop.
I just needed to know what really happened.
Why did you think it was a separate person?
There's no way to find out
if the daily executions are real,
and the Emperor stopped talking
ever since Tasuketsu ended.
Jeez, Gobo. You're getting exposed.
This is bad, for real.
Gobo?
Eren.
Huh?
Was that really the truth? Be honest.
W-Wait, don't...
Yes, it was.
What's going on?!
Oh, so you don't know about the Rights.
We'll fill you in later.
The Rights?
Looks like it's safe to talk.
The Emperor is dead.
Or rather, we defeated him.
But...
We couldn't revive the victims
or recover civilization...
Given that we're now living
in a lawless society,
our only choice to maintain public order was
to impersonate the Emperor and instill fear.
So they really were...
These guys really were just trying to protect
the world by acting as the Emperor...
There's a lot I want to say, but...
If I were to boil it down to one thing:
thank you, Current Emperor Rahazelt!
Very well, good citizen!
He still gets on my nerves, though...
He doesn't actually go by that.
Just call him Gobo!
Is that even a name?
Come on, Nishime! For real!
Nishime? Who actually are these people?
Guys!
Hikari?
Are you okay? What's the rush?
It's urgent! Hurry, turn on the TV!
KHN Broadcasting!
KHN?
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
The Emperor?
W-What's going on?
Is it someone copying Raion?
Wait... isn't this a bit different?
It can't be...
I am the Queen.
Queen?!
Who could that be?
This is a declaration of war
against the Emperor.
I'll use whatever means
necessary to kill you.
I shall become the Empress.
I won't let you get away.
I knew someone else would eventually
catch on and aim to overthrow the Emperor...
Wha—is this for real?!
W-What should I do?!
Am I gonna get ki—
Calm down!
It's too early to determine anything!
We're right here with you!
That's right!
But they said I won't be
able to get away, for real...
Well, we won't let you die.
As long as I'm alive, Raha—
Gobo... you'll be safe.
They'll have to go through me first!
"You'll be safe"? What do you mean by that?!
It means I'll join your group
and protect Gobo.
Should I not?
I mean, we don't really know you
well enough to have you join...
You have plenty of time for that.
Judging by the circumstances,
I'd say you're in a dire situation.
I agree.
Gobo.
Without you, society would
have lost all sense of public order.
You're still a needed presence here,
and I'm grateful to you, too.
Raion...
That's why I wanna protect you...
no, I swear I will.
For now, who cares about anything else?
Very well, then! You shall
become my loyal servant!
Stop being so condescending!
So what's your take on that announcement?
I assume it's a genuine declaration of war,
well-knowing the Emperor's a fake.
They took the same approach as me,
so they were likely trying to provoke us
and show they see through our situation.
Definitely a confident type.
Oh yeah, they used KHN Broadcasting.
Then the Queen will be there
if we go right now, right?
No way.
Why not?
It's a declaration of war. Why take
the risk of sending in the Queen herself?
Makes sense...
There may be an ambush
or a trap waiting for us...
But if they're just waiting to see
our next move to judge our strength,
it's natural to assume that they
don't know anything about us yet.
So we're basically evenly matched for now.
But they've made a pretty bold
first move with that announcement.
Better stay on guard.
He rationally assessed the situation
and determined all that from
just one short announcement...
He's definitely sharp, but
a different type from Saneatsu.
Either way, there's no need
to panic for now—
What's up?
That girl! Where's the girl
who came in just a second ago?!
Huh?
You mean Hikari?
Oh yeah. Where did she go, for real?
Ouno?!
I should have paid better attention sooner!
Please don't let it be too late!
Hey, where ya off to?
Heading to see the Queen?
What are you talking about?
Don't you think it's strange?
The Emperor's broadcast is usually at 23:55.
There's no telling if anyone's
watching outside that window.
Which is why I did my broadcast
at the same time.
But you noticed that announcement
in the middle of the day.
And it was only airing on KHN Broadcasting.
What are you trying to say?
The Queen didn't seem to
have any information on us.
Which means you know what she's
doing, but you're not her spy.
You have information on both, but
you won't provide that to either side...
Pretty perplexing.
Nice work.
Who are you? What's your motive?
I'm willing to tell you on a few conditions.
Yeah, we'll take any dirt you've got.
I'm willing to consider
most conditions in return.
Fine, only if you accept. First...
Immobilize.
W-What happened?!
Her head and body instantly—but how?!
He stopped her from talking?
Is he the Queen's subordinate?
Assuming he was listening
to that conversation...
Shoot!
Prime Right of Materialization!
Prime Right?!
Perfect Wall!
You stay back!
Shoot! He's getting away!
Shinozaki-san!
There!
He's behind that building!
Prime Right of Materialization!
Harpy Knight!
Bring back that guy who took off!
If you need to beat him up
in the process, so be it!
You okay, Souma?
Y-Yeah, this ain't nothin'.
So this is what the Rights are.
This is insane.
It's superpowers in real life!
My arm!
H-Hey! You're gonna kill him!
Stay out of it!
Never hesitate when going
against a Prime Rights owner.
Unless you wanna end up like Hikari!
Never forget that! We didn't fight
our way here out of pure luck!
It's not something you
can do half-heartedly...
Don't push yourself too hard, baldy macho!
Just a bit longer.
I've lost all sensation...
I don't have much time.
Kunashiri!
What's your Prime Right?
Prime Right of Immobilization.
How?! I didn't mean to answer—
What kind of ability is that?
It's because of her Prime Right!
I was able to keep quiet through resisting...
So it's not a Prime Right, but a Right.
Luckily, I didn't end up exposing
my abilities or weakness...
He resisted!
Nice Eren, you did more than enough!
Prime Right, huh? Then you're dangerous...
Attack, Harpy Knight!
Immobilize!
Harpy!
If I really wanted to kill you...
You'd die just by moving your body
even a few millimeters.
You guys, this is bad!
We'll suffer the same fate if
he immobilizes a part of our body...
I can still materialize one more beast,
but what good would that do
if they end up like that?
Shouldn't we just let him go
so we don't get killed?
Good, be afraid...
As long as you don't know the exercising
conditions, you won't be able to move anymore!
He's trying to run away?
Even with that power?
Why not do what he did to that Hikari girl?
Immobilization...
Immobilize!
Their heads fell after the fact...
His confident demeanor despite
the injury to his left arm...
Checkmate!
We have no other choice...
Don't move and listen
to what I'm about to say.
I know a way to defeat him.
He came up with a plan in this short time?
Perfect, they're not going to
pursue me. Then I can just...
Fine, we surrender.
We'll tell you everything.
Just spare us our lives.
This must be my lucky day.
I planned on just making a run for it,
but Lady Kisaragi will be happy
if I bring home more information.
Fine, let's hear it.
This card here actually holds
the key to the Emperor's secrets.
That card?
That's right!
This card shows the Emperor's whereabouts,
which is why Hikari wanted it so much.
The Emperor's whereabouts!
What does it say? Read it aloud.
Prime Right of Materialization,
Tungsten Cube!
In order for you to exercise your Prime
Right, you have to point at your target.
Descend!
D-Dammit! Immobilize!
It won't stop?! But why?!
What did they do?!
I used my Right of Priority
so the Materialization Right
takes precedence,
so that won't work.
Right?! What's happe—
W-We better not look...
Y-Yeah... You too, Gobo!
Whoa... for real?
So this is... the reality
of the world today...
These guys must have been sad
to see one of them killed,
but they were able to let it go and fight.
They're that strong... this group of people.
You were great help. Your plan, that is.
I know a way to defeat him.
This guy's Right of Immobilization...
It's likely performed
on whatever he points at,
and it's released when he stops pointing...
You with the knit hat. Place a large,
heavy object above his head.
He'll have no choice but to immobilize it
to avoid getting crushed.
Once he immobilizes it, we'll block his path
and wait for him to bleed out
until... checkmate.
Then let's use my Right in conjunction.
It'll get the job done for sure, sooner.
Go ahead.
I'm sure of it now.
You're someone we need in our group.
Let's protect the world together, Raion Ouno!
The Key
Yeah.